I
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): was a Fleet Marine Force Corpsman so I was embedded with United States Marines for all four years and then when I got out I had the Montgomery GI Bill and I began college and now I'm looking at July 1st having to pay $1,300 a month in student loans and I'm at $96,000 in debt even with using the GI Bill and paying into it myself while I was
in the military.
You served in
Speaker 2: the military, you put your life on the line for the
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): country, and you're now struggling with $96,000, our name is the student debt.
Speaker 4: Yes.
So
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): what's that going to mean to your family and your way of life?
Man 5: We won't be able to afford where we live, worry about putting food on
the table.
Speaker 6: $1,300 a month, is that the fear?
That's a hell
Speaker 6: of a lot of money.
a
Man 5: lot of money. Debt is scary. It comes with some shame. I feel like I wish I didn't have that debt. I'm worried about the impact it's going to have on my family. And it's the rate of $1,300 a month starting July 1st is going to crush us financially.